# SHUTING **ZHAO**

Orlando, FL-32819 ↑
407-954-6780 ↓
zst9394@outlook.com ☑
www.linkedin.com/in/shu-tingzhao-1497ba199 in



# OBJECTIVE

Working in tourism field for 5 years after graduating from university with Tourism Management degree. With friendly & outgoing personality, excellent self-motivated skills and positive working attitude, outstanding in working around high-volume work environment. Now seeking for opportunities to work in web developing field.



# **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Coding Bootcamp | University of Central Florida

12/01/2020 – NOW Grade average : A

# **Bachelor** | University of Hawaii & Hainan University

09/01/2012 - 06/30/2016

Rank: top 5%

Major: Tourism & Travel Management

GPA: 3.6+



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Amazon Warehouse Associate | Amazon

12/11/2019 - NOW

Self employed working in Amazon third party company -Amazon Flex. Handle the process of package delivery from warehouse stations to customer including package tracking, delivery route distribution, package delivery control, etc.

# Restaurant Manager & Server | Lee Restaurant LLC

4/05/2018 - 02/05/2021

General manager in the Japanese restaurant to make sure the high-quality customer service providing and run all the server and kitchen staffs managing process.

## **Premium Service** | Universal Orlando

1/05/2020 - 07/19/2020

Virtual line team member at volcano bay park. Provide the best experience and assistant for all the park guests.

## **Cultural Representative** | Walt Disney

10/01/2016 – 12/01/2017

Fine-dining food server in Disney Epcot Nine-dragon Restaurant. Provide all guests with nice dining experience including greeting, explaining for the menu, serving beverage & dish, merchandize cashier handling, culture representation, etc.